{
    "id": "f420cc8894034e408dee4f6675ad5ea3",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I look forward to ………………. my grandchildren.",
            "description": "When to is used as a preposition, it is followed by an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "seeing",
                "see"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They accused him …………………… poisoning their dog.",
            "description": "We accuse somebody of something.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I totally disagree …………………….. you.",
            "description": "We agree with a person.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I cannot agree ……………………… the argument that a ban on smoking violates individual rights.",
            "description": "We agree with an opinion or argument.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I must apologize …………………….. my rude conduct.",
            "description": "We apologize for something.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They will take you back if you apologize ……………………….. them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you believe ………………………… ghosts?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The loud noise from the street prevented me ……………………… sleeping.",
            "description": "Prevent is followed by from + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was quite impressed …………………… her performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You don’t have to pay …………………… that drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Once he found a good job, he got married …………………….. his childhood sweetheart.",
            "description": "Marriage is used with the preposition to.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know the reason ……………………… his unhappiness.",
            "description": "Reason is followed by for.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}